<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Ben Trevett blog</title>
<description>Posts by Ben Trevett</description>
<link>http://www.bentrevett.com/</link>
<atom:link href="http://www.bentrevett.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00</lastBuildDate>
<item>
	<title>Default Twitter Sucks</title>
	<description>I started using twitter around ~2012 when I started university. I would use it to (what is now called) shitpost and just tweet absolute garbage. Eventually, I got bored of it and deleted my account. When I started my PhD I created a new twitter account with the aim of using it to only follow machine learning researchers as twitter was (and still is) the best way to keep up with the field. The problem is: the default twitter experience sucks.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/default-twitter-sucks.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/default-twitter-sucks.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links VII</title>
	<description>Of course, like almost everybody, I stopped posting on a regular basis for various reasons. [Life finds a way](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dMjQ3hA9mEA) (to get in the way). On a related note: I didn't think Jurassic World 3 was as bad as reviewers say. Sure, it wasn't great, but a [38 on metacritic](https://www.metacritic.com/movie/jurassic-world-dominion)?!</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-vii.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-vii.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>You Will Always Be Stupid and Naive</title>
	<description>My goal for the past year was to post more, however I predictably stopped posting about three months into the year due to things -- finishing my PhD, getting a job and other miscellaneous life stuff -- getting in the way. I thought it would be fun to look back at a post of mine from the past and see what mistakes (of which there are many) I'd made, mostly because I could just spew out a stream-of-consciousness style post in order to bash something out quickly, and it would be pretty painless to write.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/you-will-always-be-stupid-and-naive.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/you-will-always-be-stupid-and-naive.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Conscious Coding Practice</title>
	<description>Taken from Noah Gibbs' [talk](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NF4rHCUElVI).</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/conscious-coding-practice.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/conscious-coding-practice.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Intelligence</title>
	<description>What is intelligence? The stereotypical example is someone who is good at math. What does being "good at math" even mean? Someone who can multiply two 10-digit numbers in their head in under a second seems to be "good at math". What about someone who isn't quick at mental math but can solve a complex mathematical problem after methodically working through the correct steps? I'd say they were also intelligent. Of course, intelligence isn't just tied to mathematical ability what about someone who can write a great novel? Or can compose a beautiful piece of music? Surely they're intelligent too, and there's no guarantee they're good at math.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/intelligence.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/intelligence.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links VI</title>
	<description>I almost gave up on posting because I have had zero motivation recently and don't think I saw a single article worth sharing. However, I sat down and forced myself to at least write something, so here it is. Less links this week and more opinions.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-vi.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-vi.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links V</title>
	<description>No website tweaks this week. Instead, I went ahead and bought an ergonomic keyboard, the [Microsoft Ergonomic](https://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/B07YGNN6N1). I've only ever used the cheapest keyboards possible -- I was only on the market for a new keyboard because the shift, backspace and control keys of my previous one kept jamming -- but decided to finally splash out.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-v.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-v.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links IV</title>
	<description>On the recurring theme of tweaking the website, the index page is now generated from Markdown too. This was mainly done for consistency with the posts and the fact that it's a lot nicer to write in Markdown than it is in HTML.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-iv.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-iv.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links III</title>
	<description>I did a third post. If you do something three times does it finally count as a habit?</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-iii.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-iii.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links II</title>
	<description>I've decided to keep up with constantly posting interesting links along with my comments and adjacent thoughts on them. It actually helps me write down a lot of things that I'm subconsciously thinking and haven't ever put down on paper or expressed to anyone else, which is good.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-ii.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-ii.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weak Links I</title>
	<description>Well, I did it. I managed to write two posts within one month, a new record. I also finally got around to installing `pandoc` and am now using that to generate the HTML for these posts. A while ago I used a static site generator, but I always felt like they took too much messing about with to configure anything. I never wanted my website to be anything more than basic HTML anyway, so I wrote everything myself. The issue was a lot of copy and pasting whenever I wanted to add a new page. Now I can just write everything up in Markdown and have `pandoc` generate the HTML, which is then added to an HTML template. Now I only have to change a single template instead of multiple HTML files.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-i.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/weak-links-i.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hello World</title>
	<description>Why am I writing this? I don't write a lot, and I'm always reading about how you should write a lot because it's good for you, both in terms of learning how to write well and getting ideas out of your head and on to a page in order to explore your own thoughts and interpretations of whatever you're thinking of. I've tried writing multiple times before, and it never took off, so why do I think this time will be different? To be honest, I don't, but I think I'm considerably better at writing than I have been before, though I still don't think I'm great. I was mostly inspired to start writing after reading [this](https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/01/04/is-substack-the-media-future-we-want) article, which also reminded me to read Anna Weiner's memoir at some point, and I like the idea of being able to write as a hobby. I don't care about being able to generate money from it, which seems impossible to do on substack unless you already have an existing audience anyway, or even being good at it. The objective is to have somewhere to spew out whatever is on my mind at the time.</description>
	<link>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/hello-world.html</link>
	<guid>https://www.bentrevett.com/posts/hello-world.html</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>